Guide to the Fales Zine Collection MSS.374
Fales Library and Special Collections
Fales Zine Collection
1990-2013
Fales Library and Special Collections
Fales Library
MSS.374
330
0.5 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box
The Fales Zine Collection includes zines donated to the Fales Library & Special Collections and zines created through various projects. The collection was created by the Fales Library & Special Collections to house the zines in its collections that did not belong to any collection already.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in four series by topic, Series I: Zines by NYU Students, Series II: People of Color Zine Project, Series III: Zines by PACE University Students, and Series IV: Various Zine Donations.
Historical note
The collection was created by the Fales Library & Special Collections to house the zines in its collections that did not belong to any collection already.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
No information was recorded about the acquisition of the materials in this collection.
Scope and Contents
The Fales Zine Collection includes zines donated to the Fales Library & Special Collections and zines created through various projects. The collection includes zines created in response to courses taught at Fales by New York University and Pace University students, zines created through the People of Color Zine Project, and zines donated to Fales through other means.
Zines; Zine libraries.
- Series I: Zines by NYU Students, Undated; 239447; 0.1 Linear Feet in 1 folder
  - Subseries A: Zines by Jonathan Berger's Students, 239448
    - Jonathan Berger's Class, undated; 239459 (Box 1)
- Series II: People of Color Zine Project, 2004-2012; 239454; .02 Linear Feet in 7 folders
  - Anarchist Panther, undated; 239467 (Box 1)
  - Our Culture, Our Resistance, Vol. 1 and 2, 2004; 239468 (Box 1)
  - Workin' On It!: Anarchist People of Color & US Election '08, 2012; 239474 (Box 1)
  - Workin' On It!: Occupy the Hood..., [2011]; 239472 (Box 1)
  - Workin' On It!: People of Color Experience Occupy Wall Street, #1, 2, 2011; 239471 (Box 1)
  - Workin' On It: Ways to Tokenize/Alienate a Non-White Person, 2006; 239469 (Box 1)
  - Workin' On It!: We Activate! We Agitate! Womyn of Color Occupy Wall Street & Beyond! 2, 2012; 239475 (Box 1)
- Series III: Zines by PACE University Students, 2012; 239449; 0.1 Linear Feet in 5 folders
  - Subseries A: Zines by Stephanie Hsu's Students, 239450
    - I Am Not Sorry, [2012]; 239455 (Box 1)
    - I Just Want Back Into Your Mind, [2012]; 239456 (Box 1)
    - Menstruate: Librarians and Archivists Keep the Information Flowing, 2012; 257037 (Box 1)
    - Queird, [2012]; 239457 (Box 1)
    - The True Diary of a Part Time Pussy Lover, [2012]; 239458 (Box 1)
- Series IV: Various Zine Donations, 2010-2013; 239451; 0.2 Linear Feet in 9 folders
  - Barnard Zine Library Zine, 2011; 239460 (Box 1)
  - A Brief History of the 23rd Precinct, undated; 239461 (Box 1)
  - Mayday 1971 or, How to Lose Street Battles and Alienate People, undated; 239462 (Box 1)
  - The Pressure To Be Happy, June, 2013; 270462 (Box 1)
  - Riot Control, undated; 239463 (Box 1)
  - Tiny Magical Adventures, Volume 1, December, 2010; 270463 (Box 1)
  - Static Zine, Toronto's Arts and Culture Magazine, Issue # 7, June, 2013; 270464 (Box 1)
  - Superstorm Sandy and New York City's Dark Recovery or, Things to be Seized During the Coming Insurrection, 2012; 239464 (Box 1)
  - Zine-O-File, Summer 2013; 270465 (Box 1)